Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - Side A: Quinn, Caramel, "Town of Galway" Side B: Quinn, Caramel, "Show Me the Road to Ireland", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Margo and the Country Folk, "I'll Forgive and I'll Try to Forget" Side B: Margo and the Country Folk, "Satisfied Mind", 1970 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie, "Do You Mind If You Leave Me Sleeping" Side B: McBride, Frankie, "Five Little Fingers", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Prince Vince and the Kings, "For Baby" Side B: Prince Vince and the Kings, "Amy", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Miller, Mitch, "Golden Harvest Sing Along", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: The Clancy Brothers, "Jennifer Gentle" Side B: The Clancy Brothers, "Beer, Beer, Beer", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Tulla Ceili Band, "Brennan's Reels" Side B: Tulla Ceili Band, "Ireland's Green Shamrock to Englands Red Rose", 1972 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Duggan, Don, "I'll Be Your Baby Tonight" Side B: Duggan, Don, "Think of Me", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: The Cyril Stapleton Choir and Orchestra, "Serenade for Elizabeth" Side B: The Cyril Stapleton Choir and Orchestra, "Cara", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: O'Hara, Shay & the Premier Aces, "So Long Mary" Side B: O'Hara, Shay & the Premier Aces, "Your Lilly White Hands", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Rock, Dickie, "Come Back to Stay", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Rising Sons, "Just A Little While Longer" Side B: Rising Sons, "Fountain of Love", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: The Dixies, "Katie's Kisses" Side B: The Dixies, "Walk Through This World With Me", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Kane, Kevin & the Arrivals, "Sadie (The Cleaning Lady)" Side B: Kane, Kevin & the Arrivals, "The Guitar", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "It's the Ring Your Mother Wore" Side B: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "I'll Take You Where the Music's Playing", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Wolf Tones, "Flow Liffey Waters" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Wolf Tones, "Flight of Earls" (empty sleeve) (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Town Of Galway" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Show Me The Road To Ireland", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Gill, Earl, "Sunset" Side B: Gill, Earl, "If I Could Choose", 1967 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "Where The Three Counties Meet" Side B: Noonan, Paddy, "Light & Lively Jigs", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: MacLeod, Jim, "March of the Penny Whistler" Side B: MacLeod, Jim, "The Happy Whistler", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie, "Do You Mind If You Leave Me Sleeping" Side B: McBride, Frankie, "Five Little Fingers", 1967 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: McDonagh, Owen, "Bogside Volunteers" Side B: McDonagh, Owen, "The Old Triangle", 1970 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Pickering, Johnny, "Medley of Jigs" and "Medley of Reels" Side B: Pickering, Johnny, "Medley of Jigs" and "Medley of Hornpipes", 1961 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: The Keynotes, "Come By The Hills" Side B: The Keynotes, "Lowlands of Holland", 1970 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Family Pride, "I'll Remember" Side B: Family Pride, "King Of The Fairies", 1973 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "Come Back Paddy Reilly" and "Slattery's Mounted Fut" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "The Risin' Of The Moon" and "Eileen O'Grady", 1957 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: MacEwan, Sydney, "The Rose of Tralee" and "Eileen Oge" Side B: MacEwan, Sydney, "Londonderry Air", "The Old House", and "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms", 1958 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Fitzgerald, Kathleen, "Beautiful Bundoran" and "Evening in Mount Melleray" Side B: Fitzgerald, Richard, "March Medley" and "Set Dance", 1962 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Bannon, Andy, "Let There Be Peace" Side B: Bannon, Andy, "Lily McNally McNair", 1974 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Foley, Connie, "Coortin' in the Kitchen" Side B: Foley, Connie, "Bold Thady Quill", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Cabaret Gael-Linn, "Bhios-sea la I bPort Lairge", "Marcach ar an Aonach", and "Ta ina la" Side B: Cabaret Gael-Linn, "An Chuilfhionn" and "An Cruiscin Lan", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Slaney Valley" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "I Was Coming Home To You", 1971 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "The Old Refrain" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Slaney", 1970 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Nineteen Men" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Old Dungannon Road", 1974 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Wings, "Give Ireland back to the Irish" Side B: Wings, "Give Ireland back to the Irish (Version)", 1972 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Kingston, Noel, "Gradh Mo Chroi" Side B: Kingston, Noel, "I Am Joe Cahill", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: McMahon, Dolly, "Sweet Rathcoole" Side B: McMahon, Dolly, "Roving Galway Boy", 1968 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Brendan, "In Person" Side B: O'Brien, Brendan, "Dream Lover", 1968 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Michael Collins" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Skibereen", 1972 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Dolan, Joe, "Does It Always Have To Be This Way" Side B: Dolan, Joe, "I Love You More And More Each Day", 1965 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: The Morrisseys, "Carlingford" Side B: The Morrisseys, "Galty Mountain Boy", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "High Germany" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "The Glen Of Aherlow", 1969 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Mulvihill, Tommy, "Days In Old Donegal" Side B: Mulvihill, Tommy, "Ha'Penny Bridge", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: The McTeggarts, "Subla Bay" Side B: The McTeggarts, "Blarney Stone", 1967 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Richards, Ron, "Kilavy's Pride", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Gloria, "One Day At A Time" Side B: Gloria, "The Old Rugged Cross", 1977 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Dwyer, Tommy, "Welcome Mr. Reagan" Side B: Dwyer, Tommy, "Cooley's Reel/Ships In Full Sail", 1984 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Slievenamon" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Seven Old Ladies", undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Clancy, Willie, "Hardiman The Fiddler", "Coleman's Favourite", "Chief O'Neil's Favourite", and "Introducing The Maid I Ne'er Forgot" Side B: Clancy, Willie, "The Tempest And Colonel Rodney", "The Chanter's Song", and "The Mountain Road", 1963 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Wings, "Give Ireland back to the Irish" Side B: Wings, "Give Ireland back to the Irish (Version), 1972 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - "McCormack Sings Irish Songs" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - O'Brien, Dermot and his Quartet, "Music of Ireland" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Cahill, Joe, "Songs of the Emerald Isle" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Doherty, Robert, "Drop Off in Ballyporeen" (empty sleeve), 1984 (Box 77, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: McKenna, Hugh, "My Eileen Is Waiting For Me" Side B: McKenna, Hugh, "The Rose Of Moray", 1980 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel and Sean Fuller, "The Story Of The Magi" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "The Solitary Life", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: McMahon, Dolly, "Hills Of Connemara" Side B: McMahon, Dolly, "Charlie", 1967 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Ould Ballymoe" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "The Hymn I Sang As A Boy", 1968 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - McEvoy, Johnny, "Long Before Your Time" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "It's Been A Beautiful Life", 1976 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Slaney Valley" and Dermot Hegarty, "Four Green Fields" Side B: O'Brien, Durmot, "Old Claddagh Ring" and Brian Coll, "These Are My Mountains", 1972 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: McManus, Dick and the Emerald Showband, "Boolavogue" and Dick McManus and the Emerald Showband, "Will Ye Go Lassie, Go" Side B: McManus, Dick and the Emerald Showband, "The Bold O'Donoghue" and Dick McManus and the Emerald Showband "The Faughn Side", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "You'll Never Miss Your Mother Till She's Gone" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "If You Ever Go Over To Ireland", 1971 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "Sweet Marie" and "Leprechaun Lullaby" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "Tobermory Bay" and "Dying Stockman", 1961 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Makem, Tommy and Ray Durham "Four Green Fields" Side B: Makem, Tommy and Ray Durham "Come By The Hills", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Drennan, Tommy and The Monarchs, "Boulavogue" and "Bless This House" Side B: Drennan, Tommy and The Monarchs, "The Swallow" and "I Can't Get You Out Of My Heart", 1964 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Douglas, Mike, "Galway Bay" Side B: Douglas, Mike, "Little Town In Old County Down", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Logan, Al, "My Kathleen" Side B: Logan, Al, "One Day At A Time", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, "Take Me Back" Side B: Daly, Pat, "Homeward Bound", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Henry, Noel, "Peace On Erin's Green Shore" Side B: Henry, Noel, "Lambs In The Green Fields", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Walsh, Chris with The Evergreens, "Connemara Cradle Song" Side B: Walsh, Chris with The Evergreens, "Riders In The Sky", 1976 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: The Irish Blazers, "The Martyr From Mayo" Side B: The Irish Blazers, "An Irish Martyr", 1976 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: The Galway Blazers, "Ireland United" Side B: The Galway Blazers, "Reel Medley: Mountain Road, Tim Maloney's, Sally Gardens", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Codd, Martin and The Herdsmen, "Whisper Your Mother's Name" Side B: Codd, Martin and The Herdsmen, "Carolans Concerto", 1969 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Duffy, Tom, "Roisin Dubh" Side B: Duffy, Tom, "Mary of the Curling Hair", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: The Swinging Jarvies, "My Kathleen" Side B: The Swinging Jarvies, "Let There Be Peace", 1974 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Logan, Al, "Gentle Annie" Side B: Logan, Al, "Twelfth Of Never", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Conlin, Jim "England You Must Pull Out Now" Side B: Conlin, Jim "England You Must Pull Out Now" (Instrumental), 1982 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "The Johnny Thompson Song" and "Flower of Macroom" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "Danny Boy" and "Black & Tan Gun", 1966 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Four Green Fields" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "When Johnny Comes Marching Home", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: The Dubliners, "Surrounded By Water" Side B: The Dubliners, "Off To Dublin In The Green", 1966 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Noonan, Paddy and His Music, "Spirit Of St. Patrick's Day" Side B: Noonan, Paddy and His Music, "The Blarney Stone Jig", 1982 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Schooner Fare, "We're Here To Drink The Whiskey" Side B: Schooner Fare, "Sweet Thames Flow Softly", 1982 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian, "Hometown On The Foyle" Side B: Coll, Brian, "If I Could Start Over" and "Silver Haired Daddy", 1974 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry And The Mighty Avons & Strings, "There's That Smile Again" Side B: Cunningham, Larry and The Mighty Avons & Strings, "Lovely Leitrim", 1965 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: The Ludlows, "The Sea Around Us" Side B: The Ludlows, "The Butcher Boy", 1966 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Begley, Philomena and the Country Flavour, "Ramblin' Man" Side B: Begley, Philomena and the Country Flavour, "Shoes Don't Fit", 1972 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: McManus, Dick and the Irish Revolution, "Miltown Malbay" Side B: McManus, Dick and the Irish Revolution, "Lullaby", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: The Byrne Bros., "Men Behind The Wire" Side B: The Byrne Bros., "Wild Colonial Boy", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "My Native Town Drumlish" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Circle Game", 1968 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Black, Mary, "As I Leave Behind Neidin" Side B: Black, Mary, "Ellis Island", 1986 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: McCormack, John, "The Rose Of Tralee" and "Somewhere A Voice Is Calling" Side B: McCormack, John, "Mother Machree" and "Kathleen Mavourneen", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Prunty, John & The Midlanders, "The Greenfields Of Longford" Side B: Prunty, John & The Midlanders, "The Old Woman From Wexford", 1985 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: The Celtic Flavour Band, "The Candy Store On The Corner" Side B: The Celtic Flavour Band, "Sweet Sixteen", 1984 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary with Paddy Noonan and his Band, "The Emerald Isle Express" Side B: Connolly, Mary with Paddy Noonan and his Band, "Gweevara Bay", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Four Green Fields" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "When Johnny Comes Marching Home", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Bowyer, Brendan, "The Rapparee" Side B: Bowyer, Brendan, "Whistlin' Phil McHugh", 1967 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: McCormack, John, "The Star of the County Down" and "The Harp that once thro' Tara's Halls" Side B: McCormack, John, "The Garden Where the Praties Grow" and "Terence's farewell to Kathleen", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Henry, Noel, "My Best Wishes" Side B: Henry, Noel, "Nobody's Child", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Where My Eileen Is Waiting" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Castle Of Dromore", 1975 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Margo, "A Sprig Of Irish Heather" Side B: Margo, "Only If There Is Another You", 1983 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Margo, "A Sprig Of Irish Heather" Side B: Margo, "Only If There Is Another You", 1983 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Henry, Dermot and The Virginians, "The Old Dungarvan Oak" Side B: Henry, Dermot and The Virginians, "Star Of Logy Bay", 1973 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Wolfhound, "Provie Birdie" Side B: Wolfhound, "Sweet Carnlough Bay", 1973 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "Charming Salthill" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "The Irish Rover", 1962 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Where The 3 Counties Meet" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Bright City Lights", 1973 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Mulvihill, Tommy, "Days In Old Donegal" Side B: Mulvihill, Tommy, "Ha'Penny Bridge", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: O'Hara, Shay and the Royal Blues, "Croce Di Oro (Cross Of Gold)" Side B: O'Hara, Shay and the Royal Blues, "Here's A Toast To You Claddagh", 1967 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "The Boston Burglar" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "I Still Miss Someone", 1967 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Wolfetones, "Uncle Nobby's Steamboat" Side B: Wolfetones, "God Save Ireland", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "A Nobleman's Wedding" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "Home to Mayo", 1968 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Fleming, Sean and Chris Ebneth, "Fiddlers Green" Side B: Fleming, Sean and Chris Ebneth, "The Lark In The Morning", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Irish Brigade, "The Hills 'Round Dunloy" Side B: Irish Brigade, "Bold 38", 1983 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "Leaving Nancy" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "Step It Out Nancy", 1981 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: Margo, "Green, White And Gold" Side B: Margo, "Teardrop From A Rose", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: Brady, Sean, "Maggie And The Farmer" Side B: Brady, Sean, "Come What May", 1984 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot and His Clubmen, "Home Boys Home" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot and His Clubmen, "Alpine Slopes", 1966 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Flight of Earls" Side B: Wolf Tones, "St. Patrick's Day", 1987 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Do You Want Your Old Lobby Washed Down Con Shine" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Carlingford Bay", 1979 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Casterbrifge Union, "Highland Paddy" Side B: Casterbridge Union, "Bold Tenant Farmer", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: Bannon, Andy and Peter Canavan, "Let There Be Peace" Side B: Bannon, Andy and Peter Canavan, "Lily McNally McNair", 1974 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: Noonan, Paddy and His Band, "Southie Is My Home Town" Side B: Flynn, Martin with Paddy Noonan and His Band, "Charlie On The MTA", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Dunlaoire" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Boyle In The Co. Roscommon", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Side A: The Wolfhounds, "Over The Wall (Crumlin Kangaroos)" Side B: The Wolfhounds, "The Magnificent Seven", 1972 (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Side A: Fleming, Sean and Chris Ebneth, "Fiddlers Green" Side B: Fleming, Sean and Chris Ebneth, "The Lark In The Morning", Undated (Box 78, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "The Green Hills of Kerry" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "I Wouldn't Be So Lonely", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Grace, Brendan, "Paddy The Pedlar" Side B: Grace, Brendan, "A Day At The Zoo", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Makem & Clancy, "Red Is The Rose" Side B: Makem & Clancy, "Bower Madden", 1979 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Morgan, Marie, "Just Keep It Up" Side B: Morgan, Marie, "Butterfly", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Gay Galty Mountains" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Jimmy Brown The Newsboy", 1969 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Stanley, Fintan, "Fiddlers Green" Side B: Stanley, Fintan, "Jigs … Rory O'Moore, Connaught Mans Rambles, I Will If I Can", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: The Black Water Boys, "The Band Played Waltzing Matilda" Side B: The Black Water Boys, "Drunken' Sailor", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Byrne, Kenny, "Boolavogue" Side B: Byrne, Kenny, "Medley of Irish Jigs", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Mary Ann Regrets" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Galway Bay", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Planxty, "The Cliffs of Dooneen" Side B: Planxty, "Yarmouth Town", 1972 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Faughan Side" and "Lady Colleen" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Co. Leitrim Queen" and "Beggar Man", 1973 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "The Sunset Years of Life" Side B: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "I'll Settle For Old Ireland", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Cottage On The Borderline" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "Three Steps To The Phone", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Cribben, Shea, "Love & The Country" Side B: Cribben, Shea, "The Girl Next Door", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Ledingham, Jon, "Without An E" Side B: Ledingham, Jon, "She's Got Me", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Ledingham, Jon, "Love Is A Toy" Side B: Ledingham, Jon, "Thank You Mrs. Gilbert", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Gregory & The Cadets, "Have I Told You Lately That I Love You" Side B: Gregory & The Cadets, "Naughty Little Girl", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie, "Forty Shades of Green" Side B: McBride, Frankie, "How Are Things In Glocca Morra?", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Kerr, John, "A Little Country Town In Ireland" Side B: Kerr, John, "Tonight In Camden Town", 1976 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat, "The Streets Of Dungannon" Side B: Lynch, Pat, "Loughlin", 1970 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Stanley, Fintan, "Wild Colonial Boy" Side B: Stanley, Fintan, "Do You Want Your Old Lobby Washed Down", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: The Irish Rovers, "The Orange and the Green" Side B: The Irish Rovers, "Whiskey on a Sunday", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - John McCormack Sings Irish Songs, Vol. 1, undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: The Barleycorn, "On the One Road" Side B: The Barleycorn, "Sing Irishmen Sing", 1972 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: The Wolfe Tones, "Deportees" Side B: The Wolfe Tones, "Rock-On Rockall", 1974 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "Gweebarra Bay" Side B: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "The Great El Tigre", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Cafferkey, Gentle Tony, "Soon I'll Be Home With You Mayo" Side B: Cafferkey, Gentle Tony, "An Undiscovered Star", 1981 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: The Chieftains, "Boil the Breakfast Early" Side B: The Chieftains, "Carolan's Welcome", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "Old Fenian Gun" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "I'm Gonna Be A Country Boy Again", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Lynn, Vera with the Johnston Brothers, "(Tell Me) What Have They Told You Side B: Lynn, Vera with the Roland Shaw Orchestra and Chorus, "Doonaree", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Carolans Kind, "Three Drunken Maidens" Side B: Carolans Kind, "Woodcock Hill & The Wonder Hornpipe", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Timon, "Bitter Thoughts of Little Jane" Side B: Timon, "Rambling Boy", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Cannon, Freddy with Frank Slay & his Orchestra, "Palisades Park" Side B: Cannon, Freddy with Frank Slay & his Orchestra, "June, July, and August", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: The Millionaires, "Winter Winds" Side B: The Millionaires, "Chime Bells", 1966 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: The Dixies Showband, "History Repeats Itself It was Only A Heart" Side B: The Dixies Showband, "The Life Story", 1966 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Murphy, John, "Lough Sheelin" Side B: Murphy, John, "I Still Miss Someone", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 36)